

## Profile

Full-stack developer with over 15 years of experience helping IT companies build products and services of exceptional quality.

Over the past two years, I led the successful launch of a new B2B product for the digital workflow and automation market as the product's PMO - managing 15 development teams that included 150 people. Developed entirely on microservice distributed architecture, this product features powerful automation Bots and unlimited one-click integration with almost any cloud service or CRM in the enterprise space.

## Employment History

Project Manager (Core Team) at airSlate, Kyiv

November 2019 — May 2020

Managing technical team with 15 backend developers

PMO at airSlate, Kyiv

November 2018 — October 2019

Managing whole new product from scratch as a PMO with 20 developers and 2 managers and grew that team to 150 developers and 15 managers.

Project Manager (Core Team) at PDFfiller, Kyiv

January 2018 — November 2018

Managing PDFfiller's Core and DevOps Team

Product/Project Manager (Workflow) at PDFiller, Kyiv

June 2016 — December 2017

Implementing workflow features

Project Manager (Mobile) at PDFfiller, Kyiv

November 2015 — May 2016

Managing PDFfiller's mobile application teams

Manager (Product) at PDFfiller, Kyiv

March 2015 — September 2015

Whole product management

Education

Master's degree FEA, NTUU 'Kyiv Polytechnic Institute', Kyiv

September 2013 — June 2009

Renewable and nontraditional sources of energy

Courses

Data science, Skillfactory

December 2019 — December 2020

**Details** 

Kyiv, Ukraine, +380932393917 dmitriy.golub@gmail.com

Languages

English

Russian

Links

Linkedin Developer CV

**Skills** 

**Project Management** 

Software Development

Agile Methodologies

Team Leadership

**Analytical Skills** 

Large-scale Projects

Stress resistant

Problem-solving

Crisis Management

Communication

**Planning** 

**Hobbies** 

Data science

Bike, Fishing